{
    "id": "b71424638b2f4266afa3b54e2827d65b",
    "title": "Too, Too Many, Too Much",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "9a50fb201a0943419e88c9d6c06baadd",
            "title": "Too, Too Much, Too Many",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "She is ……………. young to know better.",
                    "description": "Note the pattern too…to.",
                    "answers": [
                        "too",
                        "too much",
                        "too many"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "It is far …………… hot to go out now.",
                    "description": "We cannot use too much or too many before adjectives without nouns.",
                    "answers": [
                        "too",
                        "too much",
                        "too many"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "We arrived …………….. late to watch the show.",
                    "description": "We cannot use too much or too many before adjectives without nouns.",
                    "answers": [
                        "too",
                        "too much",
                        "too many"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "It is ……………. early for the shops to be open.",
                    "description": "We cannot use too much before adverbs.",
                    "answers": [
                        "too",
                        "too many",
                        "too much"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The tea is too hot …………..",
                    "description": "Objects are usually omitted after the infinitive in this construction.",
                    "answers": [
                        "to drink",
                        "to drink it",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The tea is too hot for us …………………..",
                    "description": "Object pronouns are possible after the infinitive in structures with for.",
                    "answers": [
                        "to drink",
                        "to drink it",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "You are ……………… young to live on your own.",
                    "description": "Most expressions that can modify comparatives can also modify too.",
                    "answers": [
                        "far too",
                        "far too much",
                        "too much"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I could not lift the bag because it was ………………. heavy.",
                    "description": "We cannot use too much or too many before adjectives without nouns.",
                    "answers": [
                        "too",
                        "too much",
                        "too many"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He does not like …………………..",
                    "description": "We cannot use too before adjective + noun.",
                    "answers": [
                        "women who are too tall",
                        "too tall women",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "You put ……………… sugar in the tea.",
                    "description": "We use too much before uncountable nouns.",
                    "answers": [
                        "too",
                        "too much",
                        "too many"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I am getting ……………….. calls from marketers these days",
                    "description": "We use too many before countable nouns. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "too many",
                        "too much",
                        "too"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "You will look more beautiful if you stop wearing ……………….. make-up.",
                    "description": "We use too much before uncountable nouns. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "too",
                        "too many",
                        "too much"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}